https://www.lucasentertainment.com/privacy/

This site uses cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. By interacting with this site, you agree to this use as described in our Privacy Policy.Read our updated Privacy Policy Accept Cookies
Privacy Policy| Lucas Entertainment | HD Gay PornLucas Entertainment – Official Website
Lucas Entertainment
Lucas Raunch
Sex in Suits
Lucas Cams
Lucas On Demand
Login
Get Free Porn!
JOIN NOW
Get Free Porn!
JOIN NOW
Get Free Porn!
Lucasmen
MOVIES
SCENES
Community
STORE
Blog
LOGIN
SCENES
Categories
Featured MoviesBlockbustersCruising and EncountersAuditionsDaddies, Stepdads, StepsonsLucas RaunchGay Cuckolds
SEE ALL MOVIES
Lucas Men
Lucas Exclusives
Tomas Brand
Ruslan Angelo
Max Arion
Dylan James
Allen King
JOIN NOW
JOIN NOWGet Free Porn!
Privacy Policy
I. Introduction
Your privacy is important to Lucas Entertainment, Inc. This privacy policy discloses the information practices for http://www.LucasEntertainment.com, including the types of information we gather and track, how we use that information, and with whom we share it. The purpose of this policy is to let you know how we use your personal information before we collect it. We have tried to include a link to this policy on every page on which personal information is collected.
II. Information Collection and Management
A. Personal Information
i. Information we collect
“Personally identifiable information” is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, e-mail address, home or work address, or telephone number. Lucas Entertainment, Inc. only has access to the personally identifiable information that you provide to us. For example, we cannot determine your e-mail address unless you provide it. We cannot gain access to other information on your computer.
Those who visit only public areas of the Website and who do not purchase goods or services do not need to, and generally do not, provide us with any personally identifiable information.
Those who wish to join the site, however, or to purchase products or services or sign up for our mailing list, must provide us with enough information to enable us to process the requested transaction. This generally includes, at a minimum, personally identifiable information such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and may also include credit card information. Members also select, and thereby provide, a username and password combination.
ii. How we use the information
Your personally identifiable information is used only to process the requested transaction, and occasionally to provide you with special offers from Lucas Entertainment. On occasion, for example, we may send emails to introduce a product or service that we think will interest our subscribers.
Lucas Entertainment will never intentionally disclose any personally identifying information to any third party, unless we are compelled to do so by law (for example, in response to a subpoena or court order), or if our obligation to maintain the privacy of your information has been waived or otherwise excused by you (for example, by your filing suit against us and asserting claims against which such information would be relevant in our defense). Please note that our lawyers, accountants, and/or vendors are not “third parties” for the purpose of this section to the extent that disclosure to them is necessary or desirable for the operation of our business.
iii. Opt-out policy
Because your personal information is required for us to provide services to you, you cannot opt-out of providing it and still receive those services. You can opt-out of receiving promotional emails by contacting webmaster@LucasEntertainment.com, or by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter.
B. Interactive data
i. Information we collect
LucasEntertainment.com provides a number of features that allow members to communicate with each other, such as a message board and chat room (“interactive features”). Chat transcripts and message board postings are backed up periodically in connection with our routine server maintenance, and thus may be retained for an indeterminate time.
ii. How we use the information
Lucas Entertainment does not monitor use of these interactive features. We do not use information posted on interactive features except as the author presumably intended, that is, as content on the Website (and occasionally as food for thought). We do not share user submitted information with third parties, however, any information posted is visible to other members, and is vulnerable to being copied and/or redistributed by others. Members should use reasonable caution when disclosing any personally identifiable information in any online forum. We cannot be responsible for any damages incurred as a result of such disclosure, and use of the interactive services is at the member’s own risk.
iii. Opt-out policy
Members must opt-in (for example, by participating in a chat) in order for us to collect this information.
C. Click-stream data
i. Information we collect
We also collect non-personally identifying information provided by your browser and/or our servers, such as the name and IP address of the domain from which you visited (if any), the amount of time you spent on each page and on the site as a whole, and the path you followed through the site. This sort of information is sometimes known as click-stream data.
ii. How we use the information
We use click-stream data in the aggregate to analyze trends and statistics and to help us understand how subscribers use our site. This allows us to identify areas and technologies that need improvement, and to provide appropriate bandwidth and technical support for areas that are growing. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. From time to time we may share this aggregate statistical information with partners, suppliers and other third parties, but it will not include any personally identifiable information.
iii. Opt-out policy
Click-stream data is generated by your browser and our servers, and therefore you cannot opt-out of providing it. However, some of the privacy resources listed below may provide a partial solution by (for example) allowing you to cloak your IP address.
D. Cookies
i. Information we collect
We collect certain non-personally identifying information through the use of “cookies.” A cookie is a small file that a Web site can send to your browser to be stored on your system. Some cookies are deleted when you end your online session (“session cookies”), while others may be stored on your computer indefinitely (“persistent cookies”). We use session cookies on this site to store information such as user login status (so that you aren’t forced to enter your username and password on every page). These cookies expire automatically when you log out.
ii. How we use the information
We use the information stored in cookies to personalize your website experience and to manage your online session. The information in cookies is both set and read by our server and is not logged in the process. We do not share data that we collect from cookies with third parties.
iii. Opt-out policy
You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, many areas of the site will not function properly.
E. Financial Information
i. Information we collect
We do not directly collect any credit card or financial information.  This information is collected and stored using a 3rd party payment processor and gateway as an intermediate step during any financial transaction.   This information is never used or stored on our servers.
ii .How we use the information
Since we do not collect your financial information, we do not use it for anything directly.  However, we do communicate personal data and account status information back and forth with our trusted 3rd party processors and billers in order facilitate access to a purchase product or customer service.  This includes information such as if a transaction was successful, which biller processed the transaction, and a reference code to use to facilitate customer service issues that might arise with them.
III. Related Issues
A. Information security
We are constantly striving to improve the security of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of credit card numbers, to help us keep your information secure. We will continue to implement additional security measures as new technologies emerge.
B. Online advertising
Lucas Entertainment does not use third-party services to provide banner advertising.
C. Children’s data
The Lucas Entertainment website is not directed towards children and does not collect any data governed by the United States’ Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).
D. Privacy technology
There are an increasing number of products and services are available to help protect your privacy while navigating the Web. See http://www.privacyalliance.org/resources/rulesntools.shtml for an overview of some of these tools. Please note that Lucas Entertainment, Inc. has not formally evaluated these tools and makes no representations or warranties about them.
E. Business relationships
This site contains links to other websites. Lucas Entertainment, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. For example, credit card billing is provided by CCBill. The privacy of information that you provide to those companies is governed by their respective privacy policies and not by that of Lucas Entertainment, Inc.
F. Notification of changes
This privacy statement was last updated on May 24th, 2018. A notice will be posted on our website for 30 days whenever this privacy statement is changed.
G. Questions regarding this statement
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Lucas Entertainment Privacy coordinator at webmaster@LucasEntertainment.com.
IV. Notice of Rights
Subjects in the European Union are advised of the following rights; Lucas Entertainment, Inc gladly provides the same opportunities to subjects outside the European Union. (You may have other rights.)
You may request access to and rectification or erasure of personal data concerning you.
You may request restriction of data processing concerning you.
You may request the personal data which you have provided concerning you, and you may transmit those data to another party without hindrance from us.
You may object at any time to our processing of personal data concerning you and you may withdraw your consent for future processing.
If you are a subject in the European Union, and you believe that Lucas Entertainment, Inc’s processing of personal data relating to you infringes the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation, you may lodge a complaint with your Member State’s designated supervisory authority.
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Security
18 U.S.C 2257 Record-Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement
×
Don’t Miss The Action!
Fill out now to receive newsletters, promo sales, and lots more from the Lucas Men!
TROUBLE WATCHING OUR VIDEOS?
LIVE CHAT WITH HOT MODELS ON LUCAS CAMS!
